University of Connecticut, Vice President and Chief Operating Officer Records 2006.0171
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series I: Administrative Records, undated, 1908-1986
  - School of Nursing, 1970-1976 (Box 20:, Folder 763)
  - School of Pharmacy, 1967-1979 (Box 20:, Folder 764)
  - School of Social Work, 1977 (Box 20:, Folder 765-766)
  - Southeastern Branch, 4yr Expansion Program, 1972-1973 (Box 20:, Folder 767-768)
  - Status Report on Funds, 1975 (Box 20:, Folder 769)
  - Student Army Training Corps, 1918-1919 (Box 20:, Folder 770)
  - Student Facilities Task Force Report, 1978 (Box 20:, Folder 771)
  - Superintendent of Buildings (Job description), undated (Box 20:, Folder 772)
  - Survey, 1933 (Box 20:, Folder 773)
  - Swimming Pool, 1922 (Box 20:, Folder 774)
  - Tax List, 1927 (Box 20:, Folder 775)
  - Town-University Relations, 1967-1971 (Box 20:, Folder 776)
  - Town-University Relations, 1972-1974 (Box 20:, Folder 777)
  - Town-University Relations, 1975-1977 (Box 20:, Folder 778)
  - Town-wide Liaison Committee, 1974 (Box 20:, Folder 779)
  - Trend Data for Academic Planning, 1969-1974 (Box 20:, Folder 780)
  - Trend Data for Academic Planning, 1975 (Box 20:, Folder 781)
  - University of Pennsylvania, 1972 (Box 20:, Folder 782)
  - University Chronicle Advisory Committee, 1974 (Box 20:, Folder 783)
  - University Criminal Justice Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 20:, Folder 784)
  - University Relations, Advisory Committee on, 1974 (Box 20:, Folder 785)
  - WHUS, President's Advisory Committee on, 1970-1977 (Box 20:, Folder 786)
  - William Benton Museum of Art, 1967-1979 (Box 20:, Folder 787)
  - Women, Commission on the Status of, 1972 (Box 20:, Folder 788)
- Series II: Construction Projects, undated, 1896-1970
  - Beach Hall Construction, 1927 (Box 21:, Folder 789)
  - Beach Hall Remodeling, 1968 (Box 21:, Folder 790)
  - Cold Storage Building (Museum of Natural History), 1924 (Box 21:, Folder 792)
  - Cottages, 1919 (Box 21:, Folder 793)
  - Cottages, Doyle and Murphy, 1921 (Box 21:, Folder 794)
  - Creamery, Refrigerating Plant, 1921 (Box 21:, Folder 795)
  - Dining Hall, 1919 (Box 21:, Folder 796)
  - Dining Hall/Infirmary, H. Wales Lines Company, 1919-1920 (Box 21:, Folder 797)
  - Dormitory (Hillside Road), 1962 (Box 21:, Folder 798)
  - Drains, 1896 (Box 21:, Folder 799)
  - Fenton River Pump station inspection report, 1928-1929 (Box 21:, Folder 800)
  - Gilbert Farm, House, 1922 (Box 21:, Folder 801)
  - Hall Dormitory (Men's), 1925-1926 (Box 21:, Folder 802)
  - Heating System Renovations, 1969-1970 (Box 21:, Folder 803)
  - Holcomb Hall, Women's Building, 1920-1921 (Box 21:, Folder 804)
  - Holcomb Hall, School of Home Econmics Building, Correspondence, 1919 (Box 21:, Folder 805)
  - Infirmary, 1919 (Box 21:, Folder 806)
  - Infirmary Addition/Faculty House (Lakeside Apartments), 1931 (Box 21:, Folder 807)
  - Insurance Loss by Fire (Grove Cottage, Dairy Barn), 1919-1920 (Box 21:, Folder 808)
  - Inventory--Classroom, Building, Space, Facilities, 1962 April (Box 21:, Folder 809)
  - Library Addition, 1969 (Box 21:, Folder 810)
  - Life Sciences Building, 1958 (Box 21:, Folder 811)
  - List of plans for roads and buildings, 1964 October (Box 21:, Folder 812)
  - Medical-Dental School Bid, 1965 (Box 21:, Folder 813)
  - New Road Construction, 1929-1933 (Box OS, 21:, Folder 814)
  - Pathological Laboratory construction, 1929 (Box 21:, Folder 815)
  - School of Social Work Sprinkler Bid, 1964 (Box 21:, Folder 816)
  - Sewage Disposal Plant, 1927 (Box 21:, Folder 817)
  - Sewage Pumps, K.B. Noble Company, 1927 (Box 21:, Folder 818)
  - Sidewalks on N. Eagleville Road, 1962 (Box 21:, Folder 819)
  - Space Availability and Use, undated (Box 21:, Folder 820)
  - Space Availability and Utilization, 1961 May (Box 21:, Folder 821)
  - Stamford Campus, 1962 (Box 21:, Folder 822-823)
  - Storrs Congregational Church construction, 1926 (Box 21:, Folder 824)
  - Survey of Faculty and Clerical office space, 1964 (Box 21:, Folder 825)
  - Tennis Courts resurfacing (Whitney Road), 1963 (Box 21:, Folder 826)
  - Tower Dormitories, 1964 (Box 21:, Folder 827)
  - Utility Systems additions (Sewage, Disposal, Incinerator, Central Heating Plant), 1959 (Box 21:, Folder 828)
  - Vocational Agriculture Facility (E.O. Smith High School), 1964 (Box 21:, Folder 829)
  - Whitney Hall remodeling, 1965 (Box 21:, Folder 830)
  - Women's Dormitories (Hillside Road), 1965 (Box 21:, Folder 831)
- Series III: Vendor Materials, 1916-1977
  - American District Steam Company, 1921 (Box 22:, Folder 832)
  - Ammonia Contract, 1928-1929 (Box 22:, Folder 833)
  - Bay State Elevator Company, Inc., 1927 (Box 22:, Folder 834)
  - Burroughs Adding Machine Company, 1926, 1930 (Box 22:, Folder 835)
  - C.S. Mersick and Company, 1927 (Box 22:, Folder 836)
  - Connecticut Bank and Trust Company, 1971-1977 (Box 22:, Folder 837)
  - Connecticut Light and Power Company, 1963-1977 (Box 22:, Folder 838)
  - Connecticut Medical Service, Inc., 1969 (Box 22:, Folder 839)
  - D.M. Dillon Steam Boiler Works, 1927 (Box 22:, Folder 840)
  - George Washington Law Review, 1947 (Box 22:, Folder 841)
  - H. Wales Lines Copmany, 1916-1920 (Box 22:, Folder 842)
  - Hoover Company, 1926 (Box 22:, Folder 843)
  - Lotz Asbestos Company, 1927 (Box 22:, Folder 844)
  - Obelisk Waterproofing Copmany, 1926 (Box 22:, Folder 845)
  - Parker Pen Company, 1930 (Box 22:, Folder 846)
  - Pennsylvania Coal and Coke Corporation (Webster Coal), 1929 (Box 22:, Folder 847)
  - Perfection Grate and Supply Company, 1926 (Box 22:, Folder 848)
  - Refrigerating Machinery Company (Cold Storage Building), 1927-1928 (Box 22:, Folder 849)
  - Rockville-Willimantic Lighting Company, 1921-1922 (Box 22:, Folder 850)
  - Rourke-Eno Paper Company, Inc. (Nibroc Towel Cabinets), 1929 (Box 22:, Folder 851)
  - Soda Fountain and Fixtures, 1928 (Box 22:, Folder 852)
  - Standard Oil Company of New York, 1925-1927 (Box 22:, Folder 853)
  - Vacuum Oil Company, 1919-1927 (Box 22:, Folder 854)
  - Westinghouse Lamp Company, 1918-1930 (Box 22:, Folder 855)
  - Windham National Bank (Safety Deposit Boxes--list of Deeds), undated (Box 22:, Folder 856)
- Series IV: Property Transfers and Bequests, undated, 1875-1972
  - Allen, Willard H., 1963-1972 (Box 23:, Folder 857)
  - Asylum Avenue/Lawler Road, West Hartford, 1961 June 21 (Box 23:, Folder 858)
  - Beach Charles, 1911 May 17 (Box 23:, Folder 859)
  - Beach Charles, 1911 October 16 (Box 23:, Folder 860)
  - Beach Charles, 1911 October 17 (Box 23:, Folder 861)
  - Beach Charles, 1917 December 22 (Box 23:, Folder 862)
  - Beach, Charles, William Kirkpatrick and Charles Wheeler, 1917 November 14 (Box 23:, Folder 863)
  - Beebe, Fannie, 1943 January 19 (Box 23:, Folder 864)
  - Brown, Thomas, 1927 August 15 (Box 23:, Folder 865)
  - Carder, Ellen Bishop, 1967 (Box 23:, Folder 866)
  - Cheney, Willima F., Jr., 1939 NOvember 1 (Box 23:, Folder 867)
  - Child Lumber Company, 1915 (Box 0S, 23:, Folder 868)
  - College Shakespearan Club, 1939 September 28 (Box 23:, Folder 869)
  - College Shakespearan Club, 1941 September 30 (Box 23:, Folder 870)
  - Congregational Society, 1900 February 9 (Box 23:, Folder 871)
  - Costello, Annie, 1943 June (Box 23:, Folder 872)
  - Costello, Dennis, 1919 (Box 23:, Folder 873)
  - Cummings, Arthur B., 1920 September 30 (Box 23:, Folder 874)
  - Cummings, Florence S., 1920 September 30 (Box 23:, Folder 875)
  - Day, Henry S., 1938 October 4 (Box 23:, Folder 876)
  - Doss, Bruno E., 1964 (Box 23:, Folder 877)
  - Doyle and Murphy Company, 1919 (Box 23:, Folder 878)
  - Dreier,Ethel and Henry E. and Lamb, Antoinette and George, 1919 September 27 (Box 23:, Folder 879)
  - Faculty lots, 1954 (Box 23:, Folder 880)
  - Fish and Game Commission, 1934 November 15 (Box 23:, Folder 881)
  - Fitts, John N., 1918 January 11 (Box 23:, Folder 882)
  - Foley, Edward, 1918 March 20 (Box 23:, Folder 883)
  - Garrigus, Harry L., 1927 July 9 (Box 23:, Folder 884)
  - Gillette, Herbert A., 1940 August 14 (Box OS, 23:, Folder 885)
  - Gumbart, Edward H., 1939 July 21 (Box 23:, Folder 886)
  - Harris, Lydia E., 1918 July 31 (Box 23:, Folder 887)
  - Harvey, Robert O., 1964 (Box 23:, Folder 888)
  - Hauschild, Julius, 1919 July 14 (Box 23:, Folder 889)
  - Hauschild, Julius, 1928 March 16 (Box 23:, Folder 890)
  - Hawkins, Harold, 1918 February (Box 23:, Folder 891)
  - Jacobson, George, 1911 September 18 (Box 23:, Folder 892)
  - King, Joseph B., 1906 march 28 (Box 23:, Folder 893)
  - King, Joseph B., 1932 August 31 (Box 23:, Folder 894)
  - Kritivitzsky, Hyman, 1919 September 5 (Box 23:, Folder 895)
  - Kulp, Walter and Lula, 1938 November 9 (Box 23:, Folder 896)
  - Kumpf, Mary, 1966 (Box 23:, Folder 897)
  - Lee, James R., 1937 December 1 (Box 23:, Folder 898)
  - Levy, Kathryn D., 1963 (Box 23:, Folder 899)
  - Longley, Raymond L., 1926 February 23 (Box 23:, Folder 900)
  - Longley, Raymond L., 1931 July 1 (Box 23:, Folder 901)
  - Moore, Earl R. and Lora S., 1928 November 1 (Box 23:, Folder 902)
  - Mueller, Kate and Charles R., 1918 September 30 (Box 23:, Folder 903)
  - Nichols, Charles T. and A. Lena, 1915 December 13 (Box 23:, Folder 904)
  - Osborne, W.E. (Gilbert Farm), 1922 June 21 (Box 23:, Folder 905)
  - Palmer, George S., 1909 June 15 (Box 23:, Folder 906)
  - Palmer, George S., 1911 November 2 (Box 23:, Folder 907)
  - Patterson, Estella B., 1917 December 17 (Box 23:, Folder 908)
  - Prue, Joseph W., 1945 December 10 (Box OS, 23:, Folder 909)
  - Road conveyed to Town of Mansfield, 1937 August 10 (Box OS, 23:, Folder 910)
  - Rosebrooks, Charles, 1917 November 27 (Box 23:, Folder 911)
  - Second Congregational Church Society, 1916 June 14 (Box 23:, Folder 912)
  - Smith, Edward L., 1926 March 27 (Box 23:, Folder 913)
  - Snow, Joe C., 1926 October 14 (Box 23:, Folder 914)
  - State of Connecticut, 1929 November 7 (Box 23:, Folder 915)
  - State of Connecticut, 194? January (Box 23:, Folder 916)
  - Steinmeyer, Fritz, 1926 March 26 (Box 23:, Folder 917)
  - Storrs, Augustus, 1881 April 15 (Box 23:, Folder 918)
  - Storrs, Augustus, 1890 (Box 23:, Folder 919)
  - Storrs, Royal, 1875 September 2 (Box 23:, Folder 920)
  - Storrs Congregational Church, 1929 October 16 (Box 23:, Folder 921)
  - Thorn, Charles, 1911 (Box 23:, Folder 922)
  - Valentine, Benjamin, 1918 June 13 (Box 23:, Folder 923)
  - Valentine, Marie and Benjamin (Crane Farm), 1896 January 11 (Box 23:, Folder 924)
  - Vinton, Fred O., 1926 March 18 (Box 23:, Folder 925)
  - Whitney, Edwina, 1935 April 17 (Box 23:, Folder 926)
  - Whitney, Edwina, 1938 June 25 (Box 23:, Folder 927)
  - Whitney, Minerva, 1910 June 8 (Box 23:, Folder 928)
  - Whitney, Minerva, 1915 July 20 (Box 23:, Folder 929)
  - Whitney, Minerva, 1918 March 9 (Box 23:, Folder 930)
  - Wildes, Willis P. and Olive G., 1928 July 31 (Box 23:, Folder 931)
- Series V: Student Loan Committee Correspondence, 1920-1936
  - A, 1921-1935 (Box 24:, Folder 932)
  - B, 1920-1936 (Box 24:, Folder 933)
  - C, 1920-1935 (Box 24:, Folder 934)
  - D, 1921-1934 (Box 24:, Folder 935)
  - E, 1921-1936 (Box 24:, Folder 936)
  - F, 1921-1935 (Box 24:, Folder 937)
  - Faculty, 1925 (Box 24:, Folder 938)
  - G, 1920-1935 (Box 24:, Folder 939)
  - H, 1920-1934 (Box 24:, Folder 940)
  - J, 1923-1935 (Box 24:, Folder 941)
  - K, 1920-1930 (Box 24:, Folder 942)
  - L, 1920-1934 (Box 24:, Folder 943)
  - M, 1920-1935 (Box 24:, Folder 944)
  - Mc, 1922-1934 (Box 24:, Folder 945)
  - N, 1922-1935 (Box 24:, Folder 946)
  - O, 1934 (Box 24:, Folder 947)
  - P, 1921-1935 (Box 25:, Folder 948)
  - R, 1921-1935 (Box 25:, Folder 949)
  - S, 1921-1935 (Box 25:, Folder 950)
  - T, 1925-1934 (Box 25:, Folder 951)
  - V, 1933-1935 (Box 25:, Folder 952)
  - W, 1920-1934 (Box 25:, Folder 953)
  - Y, 1924-1931 (Box 25:, Folder 954)
  - Z, 1920-1935 (Box 25:, Folder 955)
- Series VI: Photographs, undated
  - Photographs, undated (Box 26:, Folder 956)
- Series VII: Oversize Materials, undated, 1915-1975
  - (Box OS:, Folder 956)
    - Blueline drawing of Dog Lane sidewalk project, 1975
    - Blueprint of road to be conveyed to Town of Mansfield (2), 1937
    - Blueprint of transfer from Connecticut Agricultural College to Connecticut Highway Department, 1933
    - Blueprint plat of land belonging to Herbert A. Gillette, 1939
    - Land to be aquired from William F. O'Meara, 1962
    - Plat of Medical-Dental School site, undated
    - Plat of property to be transferred from Child Lumber Company, 1915
    - Plat of Prue Property (2), 1946
    - Plat of unidentified property (21.55 acres) on Route 195, undated
    - Sketch of portion of Route 195, undated
    - Sketches of Faculty Purchase area (2), 1937
    - Topographical maps of proposed 18 hold golf course (4), 1967-1968
  - (Box OS:, Folder 957)
    - Blueline of C.E.S. Building (2), 1970
    - Blueline of Storrs Property Ownership, 1964
    - Land--Brush and mowing areas, undated
    - Topographical map of SE area of Dog Lane/Route 195, 1961
    - Topographical maps of Stamford Branch (3), undated
    - Unidentifed blueprint of what could be parcels along Route 195, undated
- Series VIII: Financial Records, 1899-1930
  - Debits/Credit by individual, 1899-1904 (Volume V. 1)
  - C.A.C. Transfer Sundry Ledger #1, 1911-1913 (Volume V. 2)
  - Daily Voucher and Transfer Register, 1919-1923 (Volume V. 3)
  - Treasurer's Ledger, 1929-1930 (Volume V. 4)
  - Payroll (State Fund), 1909-1913 (Box 27)
  - Audit, 1917-1918 (Volume V. 5)
  - C.A.C. Receipts and Disbursements, 1899-1912 (Volume V. 6)
  - State Fund Ledger, 1906-1909 (Volume V. 7)
  - State Fund Ledger, 1902-1906 (Volume V. 8)
  - State Fund Ledger, 1909-1913 (Volume V. 9)
  - Account Ledger, 1922-1930 (Volume V. 10)
  - Account Ledger, 1915-1917 (Volume V. 11)
  - Hotel Register (includes charges), 1916-1917 (Volume V. 12)
  - C.A.C. Sundry cash journal of disbursements, 1899-1915 (Volume V. 13)
  - Gilbert Farm ledger, 1913-1915 (Volume V. 14)
  - C.A.C. Sundry cash journal of receipts, 1899-1906 (Volume V. 15)
  - C.A.C. Sundry cash journal of receipts, 1914-1915 (Volume V. 16)
  - Disbursements of Gilbert Fund, 1906-1914 (Volume V. 17)
  - Voucher record--Special appropriations, 1917-1922 (Volume V. 18)
  - Fee Register, 1940-1941 (Volume V. 19)
  - C.A.C. Sundry cash journal of receipts, 1915-1918 (Volume V. 20)
  - C.A.C. Sundry cash journal of receipts, 1910-1914 (Volume V. 21)
  - C.A.C. Sundry cash journal of receipts, 1906-1910 (Volume V. 22)
  - Payroll (State Fund), 1896-1897 (Box 28)
  - Payroll (State Fund), 1889-1895 (Box 29)
  - (Box 30)
    - Connecticut College of Pharmacy Certificate, 1924-1926
    - Connecticut College of Pharmacy Certificate (blank), undated
    - Storrs Experiment Station account book, 1900-1902
    - College of Pharmacy--Cash receipts and disbursements, 1926 July - 1941 June
    - Storrs Experiment Station account book, 1900-1902
    - Gilbert Farm Dairy--Receipts, deposits and expenses, 1913-1914
  - Payroll (State Fund), 1911-1914 (Box 31)
  - Payroll (State Fund), 1891-1904 (Box 32)
  - Payroll (State Fund), 1896-1902 (Box 33)
  - Payroll (State Fund), 1897-1899 (Box 34)
  - Payroll (State Fund), 1904-1905 (Box 35)
  - (Box 36)
    - President's Ledger, 1900-1910
    - Land Grant Fund (Morrill Fund), 1897-1901
    - Receivables, 1913-1930
    - Federal Board Trainees (Vocational Rehabilitation Act) ledger, 1923-1927
    - Personal account ledger, 1913-1914
  - Payroll (State Fund), 1906-1910 (Box 37)
  - Payroll (State Fund), 1917-1918 (Box 38)
  - Treasurer's Vouchers, 1909-1915 (Box 39)
  - Gilbert Farm, 1906-1914 (Box 40)
  - Land Grant Fund (Morrill Fund), 1897-1914 (Box 41)
  - (Box 42)
    - Connecticut College of Pharmacy Breakage accounting, 1947-1951
    - Connecticut College of Pharmacy Daybook, 1925-1926
    - Connecticut College of Pharmacy Accounts, 1926-1941
    - Connecticut College of Pharmacy Audit, 1928-1941
    - C.A.C. Check register, 1899-1900
    - Hartford Extension expenses, 1946-1947